



Behind Yelwa Club, Bukuru, Jos, Plateau State 930104



(+234)7053332295



johnsonolaolu@gmail.com

SKILLS

Product Design

Microsoft Office

Problem Solving

Web Development

Data Analysis

Machine Learning

Digital Markerting

Project Mnagements

REFERENCES

Seun Olufolaji

HOD Mathematics – Calvary Arrows College (+234) 817-834-2511

Jude Snipes Attah

President – Options Group International (+234) 807-866-1485

JOHNSON OLAOLUWA

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEER & WEBDEVELOPER

PROFILE

Higly motivated Web Developer with over 1 year experience in Front End and Back end with frameworks. Competent in Project Management, Machine learning and Deep technology seeking to use their vast resources to solve problems in my society. Passionate about my country and believe that the development of our local content is the answer to our problems.

EXPERIENCE

GRADUATE INTERN - (AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT) **OPTIONS GROUP** - Plateau State, Nigeria

Options Group International is a global service firm dealing with business Development, Forensic Accounting, Cyber and Digital Security, ICT, Professional services, Outsourcing, Investment and Construction.

Major accomplishments:

- Worked with IT manager to create a Training class for NYSC members
- Ran succesfull markerting campaigns for company programs

STUDENT INTERN - (AUGUST 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019)
NASCO HOUSEHOLDS PLC – Plateau State, Nigeria

Nasco Households Plc is a Nigerian National consumer goods manufacturing Company .

Major accomplishments:

- Created a new working process for sulphination process, leading to reduction of time of the whole process.
- Worked with Safety department to create new guidelines for safety which decreased accident numbers

EDUCATION



SECONDARY SCHOOL LEAVING CERTIFICATE - (2007-2013)
CALVARY ARROWS COLLEGE — Benue State, Nigeria

CERTIFICATIONS

- GOOGLE DIGITAL MARKETING (GOOGLE-2020)
- GOOGLE UX DESIGN (COURSERA & YALE 2020) -ONGOING
- INTRODUCTION TO FINANCIAL MARKERTS (COURSERA & YALE 2020)
- SIX SIGMA BLACK BELT (COURSERA & UNIVERSITY SYTEM OF GEORGIA - 2021)
- IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST (COURSERA & GOOGLE-2019)